banqueaudi.com 2017-06-18

# Bank Audi sal – Bank Audi Online Banking Privacy Notice and Information Security Tips

## Online Banking Privacy Notice

This Online Privacy Notice applies to Bank Audi’s website. The notice describes and explains how this site may collect, use and share information from/about you.

####  Collection and Usage   
of Your Personal Information

Bank Audi collects personal and sensitive information in the normal course of business to provide services to clients...

Read more

####  Information Bank Audi  
May Collect Online

Bank Audi may collect information that does not reveal your identity or does not directly relate to a person, such as information...

Read more

####  Security  
Measures

Personal and sensitive information is protected by security safeguards matching the sensitivity of the information...

Read more

####  Information  
Accuracy

Personal and sensitive information should be as accurate, complete and up-to-date as necessary for the purposes for which it is to be used...

Read more

####  Advertising

Bank Audi may advertise on this site as well as on other affiliated websites.

Read more

####  Third Party Sites

Bank Audi may contract with advertising companies to advertise products and services on websites not affiliated with the Bank...

Read more

####  Social Media

Bank Audi may use social media platforms including, but not limited to, Facebook and LinkedIn to enable online sharing.

Read more

####  Other Sites

Bank Audi may provide links to third party websites, such as merchants or service providers.

Read more

####  Notice Updates  
and Changes

This Online Privacy Notice may be subject to change without prior notice. Changes to the notice posted on this site will become effective immediately. Using the site subsequent to posting these changes means that you agree on the revised notice.

Read more

## Information Security Tips

As part of Bank Audi’s commitment and continuous efforts to keep your account and personal information safe and secure, here are a few useful tips you should follow: 

  * Social Engineering
  * Fraudulent Emails and Websites 
  * Spywares and Viruses
  * Credit Card Fraud

**Social engineering** is a technique used to manipulate people into performing actions or divulging confidential information by tricking or misleading them to bypass security measures and tools. The purpose is to gather confidential information from people through phone, email, regular mail, unsolicited text messages (SMS) or direct contact and use this information in illegal activities such as committing fraud, gaining unauthorized access to systems, etc. 

#### Tips to recognize an act of social engineering

During a social engineering attack, the attacker usually: 

  * Requests the victim to provide confidential and personal information.
  * Refuses to provide specific information or indications that may reveal his/her identity.
  * Uses different approaches and techniques that rely on confidence, persuasion, intimidation, assistance, etc.
  * Attempts to mislead and/or intimidate the victim in order to obtain quick and spontaneous responses.

#### Tips to avoid being the victim of social engineering

  * Always be suspicious of unsolicited phone calls or emails from individuals requesting personal or confidential information. Verify their identity first by contacting their organization directly.
  * Do not use contact information provided by these individuals; instead, check previous statements or other sources for contact information.
  * Always check whether the individual requesting sensitive information is authorized to have this information.
  * Do not be influenced by the attackers’ attitude and do not take what you are told for granted. Always verify the identity of the requester and his/her authority to have the information.

#### What you should do if you are the victim of social engineering

If you suspect you are a victim of a social engineering attack, immediately report the incident to Bank Audi’s Help Desk and/or your branch manager. Cancelling your credit card and/or changing your e-banking User ID and Password might be required depending on the nature of the information you revealed.
